<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<root>
    <language lang="en" humanReadable="English">
        <content id="language">Language:</content>
        <content id="first line">
            The graph below shows the time behavior of the switch gate signal, and of characteristic currents and
            voltages of the buck-boost converter. Drag the vertical (red) time-marker line with the mouse. The according
            switching states are shown in the animated circuit above. The (orange) gate-signal cannot be dragged with
            the mouse because the duty cycle is set by the output voltage controller.
        </content>
        <content id="second line">
            Normalized current: \(i = I_{out,avg}\frac{2Lf}{U_2}\)
            <br/>
            <br/>
            The right-hand applet shows a diagram of the duty cycle in dependency of the normalized load. To change the
            constant voltage ratio drag the (red) curve with the mouse. Change the actual load by dragging the red point
            with the mouse. The green line defines the borderline between continuous and discontinuous inductor current
            mode.
            <br/>
            <b>Remark:</b>
            Here the output voltage is kept constant by the output voltage controller. Therefore,
            changing the voltage transfer ratio \(\frac{u2}{u1}\) does change the input voltage.
        </content>
        <content id="qna">
            <ol>
                <li>
                    <form id="question1">
                        What is the relation between duty cycle, input voltage and output voltage (for continuous mode)?
                        (Difficulty 1)
                        <br/>
                        <input type="radio" name="question1" id="answer1"
                               onChange="iPES.BuckBoost.Questions().checkAnswer1()">\(d = \frac{V_{in}}{V_{out}}\)
                        </input>
                        <br/>
                        <input type="radio" name="question1" id="answer2"
                               onChange="iPES.BuckBoost.Questions().checkAnswer1()">\(d = \frac{V_{in}}{V_{out} -
                            V_{in}}\)
                        </input>
                        <br/>
                        <input type="radio" name="question1" id="answer3"
                               onChange="iPES.BuckBoost.Questions().checkAnswer1()">\(d = \frac{V_{in}}{V_{out} +
                            V_{in}}\)
                        </input>
                        <br/>
                        <input type="radio" name="question1" id="answer4"
                               onChange="iPES.BuckBoost.Questions().checkAnswer1()">\(d = \frac{V_{out}}{V_{out} -
                            V_{in}}\)
                        </input>
                        <br/>
                        <input type="radio" name="question1" id="answer5"
                               onChange="iPES.BuckBoost.Questions().checkAnswer1()">\(d = \frac{V_{out}}{V_{out} -
                            V_{in}}\)
                        </input>
                        <br/>
                        Duty cycle depends on other parameters also.
                    </form>
                    <div id="feedback1wrong" class="wrong-answer">
                        Incorrect!
                    </div>
                    <div id="feedback1right" class="right-answer">
                        Correct!
                    </div>
                </li>
                <li>
                    Write the KVL and KCL equations for the two operating states: switch is ON and switch is OFF.
                    (Difficulty 1)
                </li>
                <li>
                    Analyse how the circuit can be used as buck as well as a boost converter. (Difficulty 1)
                </li>
                <li>
                    Do the state space analysis of the converter system. (Difficulty 3)
                </li>
            </ol>
        </content>
    </language>

    <language lang="de" humanReadable="Deutsch">
        <content id="language">Sprache:</content>
        <content id="first line">
            Der folgende Graph zeigt das Zeitverhältnis des Switch Gate-Signals und der charakteristischen Ströme und
            Spannungen des Buck Boost-Converters. Ziehe den vertikalen (roten) Marker mit der Maus. The entsprechenden
            Schalterzustände werden im animierten Schaltkreis oberhalb gezeigt. Das (orange) Gate-Signal kann nicht mit
            der Maus verschoben werden, da das Tastverhältnis vom Ausgangsspannungs-Controller gesetzt wird.
        </content>
        <content id="second line">
            Normalisierter Strom: \(i = I_{out,avg}\frac{2Lf}{U_2}\)
            <br/>
            <br/>
            Der unterste Graph zeigt ein Diagramm des Tastverhältnisses in Abhängigkeit der normalisierten Last. Ziehe
            die (rote) Linie mit der Maus, um das konstante Spannungsverhältnis zu ändern. Ziehe den roten Punkt, um die
            effektive Last zu ändern. Die grüne Linie definiert die Grenze zwischen kontinuierlichem und
            diskontinuierlichem Spulenstrom-Modus.
            <br/>
            <b>Anmerkung:</b>
            Hier wird die Ausgangsspannung durch den Ausgangsspannungs-Controller konstant gehalten.
            Deshalb ändert eine Änderung am Spannungstransferverhältnis \(\frac{u2}{u1}\) die Eingangsspannung.
        </content>
        <content id="qna">
            <ol>
                <li>
                    <form id="question1">
                        Wie ist der Zusammenhang zwischen Tastverhältnis, Eingangs- and Ausgangsspannung (für
                        kontinuierlichen Modus)? (Schwierigkeitsstufe 1)
                        <br/>
                        <input type="radio" name="question1" id="answer1"
                               onChange="iPES.BuckBoost.Questions().checkAnswer1()">
                            \(d = \frac{V_{in}}{V_{out}}\)
                        </input>
                        <br/>
                        <input type="radio" name="question1" id="answer2"
                               onChange="iPES.BuckBoost.Questions().checkAnswer1()">
                            \(d = \frac{V_{in}}{V_{out} - V_{in}}\)
                        </input>
                        <br/>
                        <input type="radio" name="question1" id="answer3"
                               onChange="iPES.BuckBoost.Questions().checkAnswer1()">
                            \(d = \frac{V_{in}}{V_{out} + V_{in}}\)
                        </input>
                        <br/>
                        <input type="radio" name="question1" id="answer4"
                               onChange="iPES.BuckBoost.Questions().checkAnswer1()">
                            \(d = \frac{V_{out}}{V_{out} - V_{in}}\)
                        </input>
                        <br/>
                        <input type="radio" name="question1" id="answer5"
                               onChange="iPES.BuckBoost.Questions().checkAnswer1()">
                            \(d = \frac{V_{out}}{V_{out} - V_{in}}\)
                        </input>
                        <br/>
                        Tastverhältnis hängt zusätzlich von anderen Parametern ab.
                    </form>
                    <div id="feedback1wrong" class="wrong-answer">
                        Falsch!
                    </div>
                    <div id="feedback1right" class="right-answer">
                        Richtig!
                    </div>
                </li>
                <li>
                    Schreibe KVL- und KCL-Gleichungen für die beiden Operationsmodi auf: Schalter ist AN und Schalter
                    ist
                    AUS. (Schwierigkeitsstufe 1)
                </li>
                <li>
                    Analysiere, wie die Schaltung als Buck Converter wie auch als Boost Converter verwendet werden kann.
                    (Schwierigkeitsstufe 1)
                </li>
                <li>
                    Mache die Zustandsraumanalyse des Converter-Systems. (Schwierigkeitsstufe 3)
                </li>
            </ol>
        </content>
    </language>
</root>